Guide to the Yale College Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Mary Miller as dean, 1999-2015; Accession 2018-A-062
  - President's funding, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Ribicoff Prize, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Management Team, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Management Team, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Management Team, 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Management Team, 2011-2012 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Management Team, 2012-2013 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Management Team, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Mini-Management Team, 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Mini-Management Team, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Mini-Management Team, 2011-2012 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Mini-Management Team, 2012-2013 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mini-Management Team, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Sex Week, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - SSS Front Desk Staffing YCDO Office Procedures, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - University Council Committee on Alcohol In Yale college, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Urban Studies, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - UWC, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Wrexham Prizes, 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - YCC, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - YCDO Theft, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Minutes of Yale College Dean's meetings, Board of Permanent Officers meetings and faculty records, 1954-1995; Accession 2018-A-0069
  Restricted until January 1, 2031
  - Minutes of Yale College Dean's meetings
    - 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Appointment times book, 1979-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board of Permanent Officers meetings
    - 1956-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Faculty records
    - 1954-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Records of the Yale College Executive Committee, 1968-2016; Accession 2018-A-0065
  Restricted until January 1, 2092.